// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is the capital city of Sri Lanka?",
    answer: "Colombo",
    options: [
      "Kandy",
      "Galle",
      "Colombo",
      "Anuradapura"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is the official language of Sri Lanka?",
    answer: "Sinhala",
    options: [
      "Sinhala",
      "Tamil",
      "English",
      "Chinese"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What is the currency used in Sri Lanka?",
    answer: "Rupee",
    options: [
      "Euro",
      "Pound",
      "Dollar",
      "Rupee"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What is the main religion in Sri Lanka?",
    answer: "Buddhism",
    options: [
      "Hinduism",
      "Buddhism",
      "Muslim",
      "Christian"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What is the name of Sri Lanka's highest mountain?",
    answer: "Pidurutalagala Mountain",
    options: [
      "Pidurutalagala Mountain",
      "Adam's Peak Mountain",
      "Thotupla Mountain",
      "Hakgala Mountain"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What is the name of the ancient city that was the first capital of Sri Lanka?",
    answer: "Anuradhapura",
    options: [
      "Polonnaruwa",
      "Kandy",
      "Sigiriya",
      "Anuradhapura"
    ]
  },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "What is the name of the popular national park in Sri Lanka known for its leopards?",
      answer: "Yala National Park",
      options: [
        "Wilpattu National Park",
        "Bundala national park",
        "Yala National Park",
        "Horton Plains National Park"
      ]
  },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "What is the name of the highest waterfall in Sri Lanka?",
      answer: "Bambarakanda Falls",
      options: [
        "Bambarakanda Falls",
        "Diyaluma Falls",
        "Ramboda Falls",
        "Duwili Ella Waterfall"
      ]
  },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "What is the name of the most famous perahera festival celebrated in Sri Lanka?",
      answer: "Esala Perahera",
      options: [
        "Sinhala and Tamil New Year",
        "Maha Shivaratri Day",
        "Pongal",
        "Esala Perahera"
      ]
  },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "What is the name of the famous rock kingdom in Sri Lanka?",
      answer: "Sigiriya",
      options: [
        "Polonnaruwa",
        "Kandy",
        "Sigiriya",
        "Anuradhapura"
      ]
  },
];